["Quiet on the set! Quiet, please! First position, please! Rolling, action!"
Hello everyone and welcome back to another edition of Director's Cut.
I'm joined here with Liliana.
Hi!
And Katherine.
And today we're going to talk about a recent movie called...
The Hangover!
The Hangover.
All right, so it's a comedy, right?
Very much so.
It was funny and it's basically about these guys who are hungover.
Yeah.
They had a really crazy night and they can't remember what happened.
But it's not just any night, right?
Because among these four guys, there's a guy who's supposed to be married.
Getting married.
It's his wedding weekend and enough craziness happens
that they might not end up making it to the wedding,
which is the big tension in the movie.
So that's the setting.
So all four of them take a trip to Las Vegas.
They're all friends, right?
Well, except for one.
One of them is the brother-in-law.
Yes, the brother-in-law.
Of... okay.
And they make a trip to Vegas where it's very popular to have a bachelor party, right?
Woohoo!
So...
What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.
Stays in Vegas.
So you have strip clubs, you have casinos.
It's a fun place for a couple of nights, right?
Too fun, one might argue.
Too.
And so this is what happens.
The interesting part is that each friend has a different personality.
One of them is very conservative, very much attached to his girlfriend
and does whatever she says.
He's like a dentist.
Yeah, he's a dentist.
So he keeps introducing himself to people as a doctor.
He's like, doctor, blah, blah, blah.
But in reality, he's just a dentist.
So he's kind of like this sad...
Unfair to dentists.
They handle anesthesia as well.
True.
That's true.
And the other guy is a teacher, right?
An elementary school teacher and he's married.
And he's a total jerk.
And he's kind of a jerk.
He's married, but he's still kind of like a crazy guy.
And the brother-in-law is a little bit on the not so bright side.
He's unstable.
I think he is bright.
I think the joke is that he did a lot of drugs when he was in college
and so now he's kind of like fried.
All right.
And the groom.
The groom is kind of like the most balanced one of the group, right?
Yeah, definitely.
Seemingly.
So they all go to Vegas and they start off their night well
and they get really, really drunk.
And apparently, they get drugged.
Well, they're not really sure what happens
because the moment after they start drinking, it's the next day.
And we as audience members also don't know what happens.
So the story is the story of how they re-write
or how they discover what happened that night.
Right.
So it's like putting the pieces together
because you don't know either.
And little by little, you discover each hour
or every place that they were going to, right?
Yes, because in fact, when they wake up,
they're all in the hotel, which they rented this nice suite
in the Caesar's Palace.
And they're looking for the groom, right?
Right.
So he's not there.
So they start freaking out, where is he?
And they start to say, what happened last night?
One of them is naked.
And they all have injuries.
They all have black eyes or broken, you know.
One of them is missing a tooth.
The dentist is actually missing a tooth.
And there's a baby in the apartment,
but they don't know whose mom the baby is.
Carlos.
They name him Carlos.
There's a tiger in the bathroom.
They don't know how it got there.
And there's also a chicken in the room
throughout the whole movie.
All the movie, there's the chicken.
It's hilarious.
All right.
So let's listen to a clip of one of the wacky things
that happened to them.
All right, we're back.
So basically, Mike Tyson makes a guest appearance
on this movie as well.
Yes.
He does.
And he's a scary, scary man.
Yes, he is.
Is that a real tattoo he has?
It's a real tattoo on his face.
On his face.
Why?
Why would you do that?
Because it's cool.
He's a prize fighter.
He's a fighter.
Like, how scary would that be?
You're in the ring with Mike Tyson.
And he has tribal tattoo all over his face.
That's very disturbing.
And he can bite your ear off.
I know.
Can and did.
Actually, I can't imagine being in the ring
with Mike Tyson.
Or like, even in a movie set with him,
he's like buff and so scary looking.
He's very scary.
Actually, I read some place,
like, if he hits you, like, he can kill you.
Like, how am I hit?
Like, seriously, if you're not like a professional fighter,
and he's like full body weight,
or how do you call it?
He uses the weight of his head.
Heavy weight.
So imagine.
Yeah, I can't even imagine.
But he actually does take a swing
at one of the actors in the movie, right?
That's right.
And it is, well, that's part of the scene
that we just played for everyone.
Yeah, it gets worse and worse and worse
because he's not the only kind of pseudo villain
in this movie.
And actually, Mike Tyson does own that tiger, right?
He has a tiger in his home.
He's famous for having animals.
He doesn't do it for like, to save the animals, right?
He has it for his girl.
No, it's cool.
Yeah.
Like Michael Jackson and his monkey.
He had a monkey, right?
Yeah, for some time, yeah.
So yeah, the movie is interesting.
They have a lot of different adventures
and a lot of crazy things that actually seem crazy
in the movie but are probably more common than we think.
Well, that was my friend's comment.
She said, the reason this movie speaks to people
and that people love it is because everything,
every situation could have happened.
But then you just add like one more thing
and it becomes completely ridiculous.
So like, yeah, you could go out drinking
with your friends and like forget what happened.
But the fact that they were drugged is like one more.
Or like, you could wake up with some stranger
in your apartment.
Well, add one more.
It's not a stranger.
It's a tiger.
Yeah, right.
So and actually, they even had gambling issues
or they got into some gambling problems.
Well, they were counting cards, which is illegal.
Right.
So even little things like this
that are actually very popular
as well as getting married in Vegas or eloping, right?
Oh, yeah.
I kind of...
Yeah, getting pitched in lesbian.
I love it.
I think it's so funny.
Like the Elvis chapels and...
But I cannot believe that people actually do that.
Like, why not?
It's so funny.
Like, imagine like Elvis giving you, you know,
giving you away instead of your dad.
Exactly.
It's like to remember.
How many people seriously have done that?
I would like to know.
More than you would like.
Seriously, like you get wasted.
You meet someone and oh, yeah, I stop and blah, blah, blah.
You go and get married.
Yeah.
But you can annul after 72 hours or something.
Really?
Yeah.
That's what happened to our friend, Britney Spears, right?
Didn't she get her marriage annulled in like 12 hours?
Yeah.
What happened?
Your friend.
I don't know if we're friends.
Well, actually, you have to consummate it.
What?
Yeah.
That seems really antiquated.
No, but it's true.
But actually, you can read it in the law.
So what?
You have to consummate the marriage?
Yeah, if not, it's annulled.
If like at some hours, 72 hours, I don't know, 48 hours,
you have to consummate it.
If not, you can annul it.
What if you marry someone who is paralyzed from the waist down?
Well, yeah.
You'll never consummate it.
Well, yeah, you can.
Your law has flaws.
Well, no.
Okay, come on.
Do we define consummates?
Okay, no, you're getting too specific.
I don't know about that.
You should be a lawyer, Kevin.
You should have studied laws.
How do we define consummates?
Yeah.
All right.
So what did you think of the movie, Liliana?
Do you?
I loved it.
It's very funny.
Very, very funny.
Do you think it's very American humor?
Yes, definitely.
So if you're not from the States or have lived there,
would it not be as funny?
I think so.
I mean, you have to get used to American humor.
Like I have a lot of Mexican friends.
They just don't get it or they don't like it, you know?
But in Mexico, we're more used to getting all the movies from the US.
But I think it's pretty, I think it's very funny.
Even if you're not American, but you need to know about American humor.
Definitely.
But what's there to know?
I mean, they get drunk and they do stupid things.
But that's very American.
Right.
Yeah, it's like if you watch French humor or English humor, it's not the same.
It's not the same.
French humor is called not funny.
And for example, I think French humor is very funny.
Very, very funny.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
And for example, British humor, I love it, but it's hardcore like black.
Oh, I like British humor the best.
Yeah.
Yep.
So, Katherine, what did you think of the movie?
Oh, it was awesome.
Hilarious movie.
Yeah.
If I were Roger and Ebert, I would give them to give it two thumbs up.
Two thumbs up, Liana.
Yeah, two thumbs up.
Yeah, I liked it as well.
I was pleasantly surprised.
I thought it was going to be just another one of those movies that frat boy movie.
Frat boy movies are like, yeah, let's get wasted.
But it was actually pretty funny.
The plot was all right.
And the way that they presented it was more interesting.
So it kept you in a little cloud of mystery for a while until you actually figured out
what happened and where everything was.
And, you know, I liked it because there's like no, like not nothing like hardcore,
like no porn, no, you know, like bad things.
No excessives.
Exactly.
It's very, very like balanced.
I mean, you still have like values, like how he loves the girl and how they're like trying to,
you know, I think that's, yeah, the friendship, all that.
It has a message.
It does.
Do you believe it or not?
It's light.
All right.
So it was a great movie.
We recommend you watch it.
And if you have any questions or doubts, please visit our website, englishpod.com.
And we'll see you guys next time.
Bye, everyone.
Bye.